Guide to the Lucy Maynard Salmon Papers, 1818-1992 (bulk 1854-1933)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE — INCOMING
  - VC Students and Alumnae to Lucy Maynard Salmon (See also boxes 45 and 57)
    - Riggs, Anne (VC 1927), 14 Jan 1927; (1 letter) (Folder 19.4)
    - Robinson, Anne Hamilton (VC 1890), 1902; (2 letters) (Folder 19.4)
    - Rottschaefer, Helen Grow (VC 1915), 1915-1926, undated; (70 letters, 3 correspondence cards) (Folders 15.6 - 15.15)
    - Rourke, Constance Mayfield, 14 July 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 19.4)
    - Rushmore, Elsie M. (VC 1906), 1906-1925; (16 letters, 2 correspondence cards, 1 news clipping, 1 fragment) (Folder 16.1)
    - Rushmore, Elsie M. (VC 1906) — Assorted Poems, 1928-1932, undated; (14 pages) (Folder 35.6)
    - Rushmore, Elsie M. (VC 1906) — "The Service of Research in the World of Affairs,", circa 1924; (5 pages) (Folder 35.7)
    - Satterthwait, Alice (VC 1917), 18 May 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 19.5)
    - Sawyer, Alice W. (VC 1897), 1897-1899; (3 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Sawyer, Harriet (VC 1907), 5 July 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 19.5)
    - Schauffler, Rachel (VC 1897), 1904, 1908; (2 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Schwartz, Julia (VC 1896), 1898, 1904; (2 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Scofield, Cora (VC 1890), 1896-1914; (9 letters, 8 TS) (Folder 16.2)
    - Schermerhorn, Elizabeth W. (VC 1889), 1916-1927; (6 letters, 1 postcard, 1 fragment) (Folder 16.3)
    - Scranton, Henriette I. (VC 1896), 1898, [1901], undated; (3 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Seaman Louise H. (VC 1915), 1919-1922; (4 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Sewall, Kate Strong (VC 1891), [1906], 1914, 1926; (6 letters) (Folder 19.6)
    - Siusabaugh, Henrietta (VC 1896), 1900, 1904, 1906; (4 letters) (Folder 19.6)
    - Sisson, Mildred H. (VC 1909-1916), 15 Feb [1915]; (1 letter) (Folder 19.6)
    - Sleight, Josephine N., 9 Sep 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 19.6)
    - Smith, Frances A. (VC 1895), [1907], 1913; (2 letters) (Folder 19.6)
    - Smith, Katharine, 23 Jan 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 19.6)
    - Smith, Louise Russell, 11 Feb 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 19.6)
    - Smyth Letitia Jean (VC 1897), 27 Feb 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 19.6)
    - Spaulding, Elsie Myers (VC 1895), 23 Dec 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Spaulding, Sarah G. (VC 1896), 30 Dec 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Starbuck, Kathryn (VC 1911), 19 Sep 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Stevens, Florence Balance (VC 1896), 13 June 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Stickney, Edith (VC 1919), 1919-1926; (7 letters) (Folder 16.4)
    - Storke, Sophia D. (VC 1870), 1894; (3 letters) (Folder 19.7)
    - Strong, Eliza L.M. (VC 1888), 27 June [1894]; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Stryker, Florence E. (VC ex-1901), 4 Nov 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Sullivan, Florence (VC 1910), 25 July 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 19.7)
    - Taylor, Katharine (VC 1910), 1915-1917; (7 letters, 1 enclosure, 2 correspondence cards) (Folder 16.6)
    - Taylor, Ruth (VC 1909), 6 Jan 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Thompson, Helen D. (VC 1899), 16 Sep 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Thresher, Irene K. (VC 1921), 11 Feb 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Tompkins, Elizabeth Knight (VC 1889), 9 Aug 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Tompkins, Juliet Miller, 28 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Toye, Rebecca W. (VC 1892), 15 Mar 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Traver, Hope (VC 1896), 1901-1919; (11 letters) (Folder 16.5)
    - Turner, Julia Emery (VC 1895), 1921-1925, undated; (7 letters) (Folder 16.7)
    - Vanderbilt, Mabel T. (VC 1901), 2 Jan 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Vickroy, Clara E. (VC 1891), 1895-1896; (3 letters) (Folder 19.8)
    - Vogel, Margaret G. (VC 1917), 23 Feb 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 19.8)
    - Wagner, Mary S. (VC ex 1895), 1901-1902, undated; (37 letters) (Folders 16.8 - 16.9)
    - Walker, A. Leslie (VC 1906), 22 Apr 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 19.9)
    - Waller, Evangelina H. (VC 1924), 1925; (2 letters) (Folder 19.9)
    - Ward, Vassie J. (VC 1897), 1917; (2 letters) (Folder 19.9)
    - MacCracken, [Henry Noble] to Vassie Ward, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 19.9)
    - Warner, Agnes H. (VC 1930), undated; (1 letter) (Folder 19.9)
    - Warner Martha L. (VC 1868), 13 Apr 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 19.9)
    - Warren, Constance (VC 1904), 1904-1920; (11 letters) (Folder 16.10)
    - Warren, Katharine (VC 1904), 1889-1906; (6 letters) (Folder 16.11)
    - Wedge, Ruth P. (VC 1915), 28 May 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 19.9)
    - Welborn, Mary Catherine (VC 1921), 24 Nov 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wellington, Elizabeth Elliot (VC 1902), 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wells, Emilie Louise (VC 1894), 6 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Werne, Mabel Rodney (VC 1890), 22 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wertheimer, Mildred S. (VC 1917), 1919, 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wheelock, Julia (VC 1903), 5 Nov 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wilbur, Mary G. (VC 1912), 15 Jan 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wilcox, Alice (VC 1894), 3 Oct 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wilcox, Beatrice C. (VC ex-1888), 1904, 1910, 1923, undated; (6 letters) (Folder 19.10)
    - Wilkerson, Elizabeth (VC 1898), 24 Sep 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 19.11)
    - Williams, Judith B. (VC 1912), 1915-1921; (8 letters) (Folder 16.12)
    - Williams, Lucretia Justice (VC 1898), 1898, 1918 undated; (4 letter) (Folder 19.11)
    - Wilson, Catherine (VC 1923), undated; (1 card) (Folder 19.11)
    - Wilson, Florence O. (VC 1912), 1913, 1919, undated; (2 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 19.11)
    - Winnington, Laura (VC 1896), 16 Apr 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 19.11)
    - Wood, Harriet A. (VC 1893), 1896, 1916, 1924; (3 letters) (Folder 19.11)
    - Wortendyke, Eleanor E. (VC 1906), 1926, undated; (1 letter, 1 card) (Folder 19.11)
    - Zen, Sophia Chen (VC 1919), 1919-1924, undated; (15 letters, 5 postcards) (Folders 16.13 - 16.14)
  - Historians to Lucy Maynard Salmon
    - Adams, E.D., 1918-1922; (3 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Adams, George B., 1895-1906, 1923; (12 letters) (Folder 23.5)
    - Adams, Henry G., 1884, 1897; (2 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Adams, H.B., 1886, 1890, 1900; (9 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Amesbury, E., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Babuf, F., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Baker, Ray Stannard [re: Woodrow Wilson], 1925-1926; 5 TLs, 1 ALs (Folder 47.38)
    - Barnes, Mary E., 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Beard, Charles A., 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Becker, Carl, 1921, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Bond Jr., Beverley W., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Botsford, George Willis, 10 Mar 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Bourne, Edward G., 23 Apr 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Bourne, Henry E., 1903-1905, 1919, 1922; (9 letters, 3 enclosures) (Folder 20.3)
    - Burr, George L., 1889-1921, undated; (24 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 23.9)
    - Bryce, James, 1894, 1898; (4 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Channing, Edward, 1895-1896; (3 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Cheyney, E., 1908- 1920; (6 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Duley, Frank L., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Dutcher, George M., 1921-1922, 1926; (4 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - Ellis, Ellen Deborah, 1918; (3 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - Emerton, Ephraim, 30 June 1888; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Farraud, Max, 1899, 1901; (3 letters) (Folder 47.14)
    - [Fink?], G., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Firth, Charles H., 4 Mar 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.14)
    - Fish, Carl Russell, 1901-1918, undated; (11 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 24.3)
    - Ford, Worthington C., 1917, 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 24.3)
    - Greene, Evarts B., 1919-1920; (2 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Gibbons, H. B., 11 Oct 1898; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Griffis, William Elliot, 1 Nov 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1887-1901; (13 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Haskins, Charles H., 1898-1906; (7 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Howland, Arthur C., 28 Jan 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Jameson, J. Franklin, 1895-1924; (8 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 24.8)
    - Lang, Henry R., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Jenks, Jeremiah W., 23 Feb 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Leland, W. G., 1912-1913; (3 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Lee, Guy Carlton, 24 Jan 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Lingelbach, William E., 8 Jan [1912]; (1 letter, 1 transcript) (Folder 47.15)
    - Lingley, Charles R., 1921; (2 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Mace, W.H., 1890, 1901; (2 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Matthews, Albert, 17 Nov 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Marzow, Lisa, 2 Feb 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - McClaughlin, Andrew C., 1897-1922, undated; (9 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - McMaster, John B., 21 Jan 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 47.15)
    - Meek, Charles S., 1901; (2 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Munro, D.C., 1901-1919; (5 letters) (Folder 47.15)
    - Nashdull, H., 30 Nov [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Notestein, Wallace, 1921-1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Owen, Thomas M., 18 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Paltsits, Victor H., 1908-1917; (9 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Paxson, Frederic L., 1908, 1913; (3 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 24.13)
    - Relf, Frances H., 1921-1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Robinson, James H., 1901-1905, 1921, undated; (11 letters) (Folder 25.2)
    - Schlesinger, A.M., 3 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Shepherd, William R., 28 Nov 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Shotwell, J. T., 4 June 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Sioussat, St. George L., 20 Jan 1913; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Stephens, H. Morse, 1895-1905; (9 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Taylor Henry Osborn, 1922-1926; (7 letter) (Folder 25.5)
    - Thayer, William R., 1918; (2 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Thwaites, Reuben G., 18 May 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Tout, Thomas Frederick, 1898, 1921; (2 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Turkey, United States Consulate-General in, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Turner, Frederick Jackson, 1902, 1909-1910; (3 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit, 1884-1898; (8 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Vicent, J. M., 1901; (2 letters) (Folder 47.16)
    - Westermann, W.L., 8 Sep 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - White, Andrew D., 1 May 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.30)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1886-1888, undated; 7 ALS, 7 envelopes (Folder 47.34)
    - Winsor, Justin, 12 Apr 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.16)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified, undated; (1 letter, 2 envelopes, 1 advertisement) (Folder 47.16)
  - Correspondence from Others
    - Abbe, Catharine A.B., 2 May 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Abbot, Lawrence, 27 Feb 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 23.4)
    - Abbott, Arletta, 5 Oct 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 23.4)
    - Abbott, Edith, 2 Dec 1909; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Abel, Mary H., 1897, 1902; (7 letters) (Folder 23.4)
    - Achert, Emilie, 1900-1901; (2 letters) (Folder 23.4)
    - Adams, Charles Kendall, 1886-1887; (2 letters) (Folder 23.5)
    - Addams, Jane, 26 Nov 1909; (1 photocopy - original housed in Autograph Collection) (Folder 45.16)
    - Albright, Leila R., 1 June 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Allen, Annie, 29 Apr 1913; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Allen, W. May, 27 Oct 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Allenson, Alice, 29 Apr 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Allison, W. B., 3 Dec 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Allyn and Bacon, 1902- 1903; (3 letters) (Folder 23.5)
    - Ames, Herman V., 1901-1902; (18 letters) (Folder 20.1)
    - Anderson, Bingley, 14 Mar 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Anderson, Winifred, [July 1916]; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Andrews, Charles M., 22 Dec 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Anderson, A.H., 11 Nov 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Anderson, Biug Ley, 6 Aug 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Anderson, Mary A., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Anderson, N.W., 27 May 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Andrews, Benjamin R., 1914; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Andrews, Lucy C., 19 Dec 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 23.5)
    - Angell, James B., 1886-1903; (15 letters, 1 correspondence card) (Folder 20.2)
    - Anti-Saloon League of New York, 23 May 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 29 July 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Arnold, J. R., 1891; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Atherton, Caroline S., 6 Dec 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Babbott, Frank L., 5 June 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Backus, Helen H., 1890, 1897; (4 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Backus, Herman H., 1901, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 23.6)
    - Bacon, C. G., 22 Feb 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Bacon, George A., 26 Sep 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Baker, Mary Hine, 24 Sep 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Balch, Emily Greene, [1889]- 1890, undated; (4 letters) (Folder 23.6)
    - Baldwin, Ruth S., 28 June 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Bancroft, James, 1886; (3 letters) (Folder 23.6)
    - Banks, Jessie F. A., 21 Nov 1889, undated; (2 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 23.6)
    - Banks, J. S., 22 Jan 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Banks, Louis Allen, 1916, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Barker, Eliza L., 9 May 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Barnes, Mary S., 1891, 1898; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Barnwell, James G., 5 June 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Barry, Edmund D., 5 July 1887(1 letter) (Folder 23.6)
    - Barrus, Annie H., 20 June 1926(1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bates, Katharine Lee, 1898-1922, undated; (14 letters, 1 card, 1 photograph, 1 fragment) (Folder 23.7)
    - Beal, Junius E., 1922, 1926; (2 letters) (Folder 23.7)
    - Beard, A. F., 7 Feb 1898; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Beard, Mary S., 22 Nov 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Beck, E. S., 1 May 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Beckwith, Frances A., 15 Mar 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bell, Annie G., 1886, 1890; (2 letters) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bell, Fred S., [circa 1875]; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Benedict, Bertram, 1918-1919; (4 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Benneson, Cora A., 1887; (2 letters) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bentson, J.W., 2 June 1892; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Benton, Eliza, 12 June 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bicknell, Mary, 31 Jan [1890]; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Bishop, William Warner, 6 July 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Blackburn, F.A., 20 Jan 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 23.7)
    - Blake, Katharine A. (VC 1880), 13 Oct 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Blatch, Harriot Stanton (VC 1878), 1897, 1900, 1925, undated; (7 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Bliven, Bruce, 5 Feb 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Boeckel, Florence, 25 Feb 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Bond, S. A. F., 25 Sep 1885; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Bonham, Milledge L., Jr., 12 Jan 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Booth, Lenora Hour, 1906; (2 letters) (Folder 23.8)
    - Booth, William S., 24 Aug 1904, 1910; (2 letters) (Folder 23.8)
    - Bourden, Lucy Salmon, [circa 1903]; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Bowerman, George F., 13 Feb 1911; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Bowis, W. F., 8 Nov 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Boyd, Emma, 1 Aug 1908; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Boynton, Fanny, 10 June 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brackett, Anna C., 1894; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Brackett, Antoinette Newell, 14 Nov 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Bradley, Phillip, 7 Mar 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Brands, A. M., 15 Jan 1891; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Briggs, Elizabeth, 1903, 1910-1911; (4 letters) (Folder 23.8)
    - Briggs, Phebe, 14 Oct 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - [Brinscanan?], Florence, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Brooks, Kato M., 19 June 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brooks, John Graham, 21 March 1898; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brouillette, Lelia, 24 Oct 1892; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brown, Jeanette S., 1887-1916; (8 letters) (Folder 20.4)
    - Brown, Mary Spalding, 4 Oct 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brown, Renee C.E., 8 Aug 1902; (1 letter) (Folder 23.8)
    - Brownwell, W. C., 17 June 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Bryan, Elmer B., 1912, 1917, 1920; (5 letters) (Folder 23.9)
    - Bryan, Julian Scott, 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Burstall, Sara A. and one from Catherine Chisholm, 1919; (3 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Burt, Alice, [circa 1896], 1904-1905; (3 letters) (Folder 23.9)
    - Burt, Benjamin Chapman, 1875, 1890; (2 letters) (Folder 23.9)
    - Burt, Barbara C. (with letter from Bart Ayoder), 1889-1905; (14 letters, 1 photocopy) (Folder 20.5)
    - Burt, Fannie S., 1897, 1902; (2 letters) (Folder 23.9)
    - Burt, Lelia Y. (with letter from A.P. Funnelle to Mrs. Burt in 20.6), 1881-1898; (106 letters) (Folders 20.6 - 20.15)
    - Burt, Lelia Y. (with letter from Barbara Burt in 21.2), 1899-1926; (39 letters, 1 correspondence card, 1 enclosure) (Folders 21.1 - 21.3)
    - Butler, Michael, 1901-1902; (4 letters) (Folder 23.9)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1890-1891, 1902; (7 letters) (Folder 45.16)
    - Butts, W., 5 Apr 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 45.16)
    - Cabell, M. V. E. (Folder 47.17)
    - Cabot, Richard C., 29 Mar 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Caldwell, J. O., 24 Dec 1887; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - Caldwell, Otis, 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Calterall, Ralph C. H., 17 Apr 1911; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - Capps, Edward, 5 Apr 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Carden, [Itiae?], undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Carmen, C.L., 1921; (4 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Carpenter, B., 1921; (3 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Castle, E. H., 10 June 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Cattell, J. M., 15 Mar 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Chamberlin, Rose (with 2 telegrams to Rose), 1886-1892; (7 letters) (Folder 21.4)
    - Chandler, Anna M., 29 Sep [1887]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - Chandler, Eva, 1887; (2 letters) (Folder 24.1)
    - Chancy, A. Cole, 1905; (2 letters) (Folder 24.1)
    - Choate, Joseph A., 24 Oct 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - [Chons?], Alice A., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clark, C. U., 1919, undated; (2 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clark, J. B., 1889; (3 letters) (Folder 24.1)
    - Clark, John B., 5 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clark, Kate, Upson, 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clark, Mary Vida, 1922-1923, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clarke, John M., 14 May 1908; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clements, William L., 1923-1924; (3 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Clulow, H.V. (with contract in 21.5), 1921-1924; (52 letters, 1 enclosure) (Folders 21.5 - 21.7)
    - Cole, Henry E., 11 June 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Coleman, Everett W., 1 July 1893; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Collin, Laura B., undated; (2 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Connell, Mary, 1922, 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 47.17)
    - Converse, A.D., January 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Cook, Thomas and Son, 24 Apr 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Cooke, M. Theresa, 19 Sep [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Coolidge, Archibald Cary, 25 Apr 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Cosson, Juliet, 8 Dec 1892; (1 letter) (Folder 47.17)
    - Cotton States and International Exposition, 1895; (2 letters) (Folder 47.18)
    - Coykendall, B.D., 22 Oct 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - Crawford, Nelson Antrim, 16 Jan 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - Cutcheon, Byron M., 1888-1889; (3 letters) (Folder 24.1)
    - Daily News, 8 Aug 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dalbear, A.E., 1889; (2 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - Daniels, Anne, 1888-1926; (10 letters, 1 greeting card) (Folder 21.8)
    - Daniels, C. E., 1881-1882; (2 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - Daniels, E.P., 1881, 1888; (2 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - Darling, Grace, 30 Sep 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - Davenport, W. E., 26 Dec 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - Davis, Elmer (Folder 47.18)
    - Davis, Elmer, 1916; (2 letters) (Folder 47.18)
    - Davis, Horace A., 5 July 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Davis, Louise S., 24 Dec 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dewey, Alice C., 13 July [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dewey, Davis R., 1892; (2 letters) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dewey, John, 13 July 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - Dewey, Melvil, 17 May 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - De Roode, Albert, 21 Mar 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - D’ooge, B.L., 7 June 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - D’ooge, Martin L., 12 June 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - Diack, Katherine S., 5 May 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dietrich, Ellen Battelle, 6 Dec 1894; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dodd, L. Wilson, 9 May 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dodge, Grace H., 1890; (2 letters) (Folder 47.18)
    - Donnelly, Francis P., S. J., 1915-1918, 1926, undated; (7 letters, 1 transcript, 3 cards) (Folder 47.18)
    - Duggan, Stephen P., 1920-1921, 1924; (3 letters) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dutton, J.E., 1889; (3 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - Dwight, William B., 28 June 1893; (1 letter) (Folder 24.2)
    - Dydyieslra, M., 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Dyer, Louis, 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 47.18)
    - Eaton, Isabel, 1900-1901; (2 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Eaves, Lucile, 5 May 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Edmunds, George, 23 Nov 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Eiley, Elsie, 14 Mar 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Elder, Louise, [1916?], 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Ellery, Frank M., 1921-1924; (6 letters) (Folder 21.9)
    - Elting, [Strong?], 27 Sep 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Emerick, Libbie, 14 June 1876; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Engles, John F., 12 Oct 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Estes, Sarah E., 14 Sep 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Evants, A. W., 1892; (2 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Farnum, Henry W., 9 Feb 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Farrier, Robert E., 3 May 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Ferdon, John, David M. Finley, and W. K. Shier, 1875; (1 card) (Folder 24.3)
    - Fogarty, Helen K., 23 Dec 1911; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - [Ford?], Earl W., 25 Nov 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Foster, William T., 22 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Freeman, Alice, 1874, 1887; (2 letters, transcript) (Folder 24.3)
    - Friedenwald, Herbert, 3 Jan 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Frieze, Henry L., 12 June 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.3)
    - Gable, Ben J., 30 Dec [circa 1887]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Gardner, Alice May, 20 Jan 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Garfield, Henry Augustus, 19 June 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Garrett, Miss, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Garrison, George P., 17 Mar 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 47.19)
    - Garrison, Wendell Phillips, 1895, 1899; (3 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Gavit, John P., 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Geris, Marion S., 6 Mar 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Gibson, Ann E., [circa 1887]; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Gilchrist, Kate, 1881-1884; (4 letters) (Folder 24.4)
    - Gill, Laura Drake, 1909-1911; (3 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Gilman, Arthur, 17 July 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Ginn and Company, 1915-1916; (2 letters) (Folder 47.19)
    - Glass, Grace J., 9 Mar 1913; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Glass, Cleova, 12 August 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Glenn, Helen, 6 Sep 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)
    - Goodrich, Nathaniel L., 9 Apr 1913; (1 letter) (Folder 24.4)